adzzoo.net 2016-05-11

# Privacy Policy | AdzZoo.com

####   
Our Commitment: Respecting and Protecting Your Privacy

Effective as of March 1, 2009

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to give you a summary of the ways in which AdzZoo collects, maintains, and uses your information. Please feel free to contact us by email at support@AdzZoo.com or by mail at AdzZoo, Privacy Department, 1601 Zack Hinton Parkway, STE 1601, McDonough, GA 30253 with any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information we gather about you.

## How We Collect Your Information

We gather information about you as you use our websites, contact our customer service representatives, fill out online order forms or information request sheets, and provide your information to our sales agents. We may use cookies and pixel tags to track your usage of our websites. We also use online order forms and information request sheets to obtain information from you necessary to process your orders and provide you with requested information. When you call the numbers on our websites and speak with our customer service representatives, we collect information provided during the call to ensure the best quality of service and the correct processing of your orders.

## Information We Collect

We collect various types of Customer Information. A summary of the types of information that we collect is set forth below:

## Customer Contact Information.

Your Customer Contact Information is any information needed to contact you and fulfill your orders and requests such as your name, address, phone number, fax number, and email address.

## Private Customer Information. 

Private Customer Information is that information that may be necessary to check credit and process payments. Such information includes your Social Security Number, credit card information, and banking and wiring information.

## Customer Order Information.

Customer Order Information is that information necessary to complete your orders and requests for information. Such information may include your Customer Contact Information, programming and packaging selections, your billing and shipping information, as well as other details pertaining to your order of products and services through us.

## Demographical Information. 

Demographical Information is publicly available information that we may learn about you regarding such things as your age, income, home ownership, household size, etc. that helps us to provide you with better offers for products and services.

## Website Usage Information. 

Website Usage Information is information that we collect that tells us about the way you use and navigate through our websites.

## Security Measures

AdzZoo has implemented a variety of encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect information stored in our computer systems from unauthorized access. We also maintain procedural safeguards that restrict access to your Customer Information to employees (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) who need to know your Customer Information in order to provide the products and services that you request. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant its complete security. We shall not be responsible for harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality in respect to your use of the Site or any information you transmit to the Site.

## Use and sharing of customer information

All of your Customer Information is used in an effort to process your orders and requests and to provide you with the products and services you desire. We may share your Customer Information with third parties in order to complete your purchases of products and services as described below. In addition, your Customer Information may be used and shared in an effort to present to you other special offers and promotions that may become available. The extent to which we use and share your Customer Information depends upon the nature of and purpose for which we use and share it. A summary of how we share your Customer Information with third parties is set forth as follows:

## With Third Party Product and Service Providers. 

We may share your Customer Information, as needed, to third parties who help us provide the products and services you request.

## With Third Party Advertisers. 

Although we never share your Private Customer Information with any third parties, except with the Third Party Product and Service Providers described above on a need to know basis, we may share other types of your Customer Information with third party advertisers who are able to use that information to provide you with special offers or promotions. The ways in which such advertisers may subsequently use your Customer Information is governed by their own privacy policies and procedures. You may opt out from having us share your Customer Information with Third Party Advertisers by following the steps in the next section.

## Website visitors

## Information about you may be used to add you to our email subscription list, provide your name to AdzZoo Independent Representatives (hereafter “AIR”) in connection with your expressed interest in our products and/or business opportunity, analyze trends and statistics, enhance the operation of the Site, serve content and advertisements and send informational and promotional materials about the Company and other companies. 

Customers

Information about customers will be used to provide customer service, confirm and fulfill orders, ship orders, and/or administer payments and possible problems or disputes with dispatchers and other service providers.

## Choice

We have existing business relationships and may develop other relationships in the future with business partners. In these instances, we may share or otherwise allow access to information that is collected about you that will enable our business partners to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest.

At the time we collect your information you will be given the choice to accept or refuse the disclosure of your information for such marketing purposes, and for marketing by the Company.

## Opt-out Procedures

To opt out from receiving further communications from us regarding other offers and promotions, or to opt out from having your information shared with any Third Party Advertisers, you may email us at support@AdzZoo.com or write to AdzZoo, Privacy Department, 1601 Zack Hinton Parkway, STE 1601, McDonough, GA 30253. 

## Telemarketing

IMPORTANT - PLEASE READ: By providing your contact information, including your telephone number, on this Web site, you are expressly granting us permission to contact you even though you may have previously chosen to have your telephone number added to any Do-Not-Call List including lists maintained by us, or any local, state or federal government agency. In addition, your state may have laws that prevent us from calling you on your mobile/cellular telephone. 

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our business. If we change how we use your Customer Information or the purposes or entities for and to which we disclose your Customer Information we will post the policy change notification on our web site.

## Access or Corrections to your information

If you identify any inaccuracy in your personal information, or if you need to make a change or would like to verify such information, please contact us so that we may update your information in our records. You may contact us by emailing support@AdzZoo.com or write to AdzZoo, Privacy Department, 1601 Zack Hinton Parkway, STE 1601, McDonough, GA 30253. We may ask you to pay an administrative fee for accessing or copying your information, but will inform you of the anticipated charges and confirm that you want us to proceed before processing your request. If you believe that the Customer Information about you that we have collected is incomplete or inaccurate, AdzZoo will correct the information upon verification of the omission or error and that the person requesting the change is the person about whom the Customer Information relates.

## Complaints

The Company takes privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that the Company has not complied with this Privacy Policy, you may write to the address below or call us. Please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Company Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your complaint, or your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, you should contact the Compliance Department, which will serve as a liaison with the Company to resolve your concerns. Contact details for the Compliance Department are as follows: compliance@AdzZoo.net.

## Modification to this Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 29, 2009. The Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon notice, which may be provided to you via e-mail or by posting the latest version on our Site. Your subsequent use of the Site is deemed as acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure familiarity with its most current version. You can easily confirm whether any revisions have been posted since your last visit by checking the date on which the Policy was last revised, which is set forth at the bottom of this Policy. If you object to such changes, we will honor our prior privacy policies as to any data previously collected. If you disagree with the changes in our policy, however, please do not use the Site after the posting of such changes online. By using the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to all such changes.

## Question comments or to contact us

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or you wish to access or make changes to information we have about you, please contact the company. Company contact information is listed on our website Adzzoo.net.

## If You Are a Resident of California

If you are a California resident, in addition to the rights set forth above, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of your Customer Information with third parties, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. California law provides that you have the right to submit a request to us at the designated address and receive the following information:

> the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for the third parties direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year 
> 
> the names and addresses of third parties that received such information: and  
>  if the nature of a third party's business cannot be reasonably determined from the third party's name, examples of the products or services marketed.  
> 
> 
> You are entitled to receive a copy of this information in a standardized format and the information will not be specific to you  
>  individually. Our designated email address for such requests is support@adzZoo.com.

## Spam Policy

AdzZoo LLC. (hereafter lithe Company) strictly prohibits the sending of unsolicited bulk email (SPAM). SPAM is defined for this purpose as sending ten or more messages similar in content to any persons, entities, newsgroups, forums, email lists, or other groups or lists unless prior authorization has been obtained from the email recipient or unless a business or personal relationship has already been established with the email recipient. The Company also prohibits using false headers in emails or falsifying, forging or altering the origin of any email in connection with the Company, and/or its products and services. The Company prohibits engaging in any of the foregoing activities by using the service of another provider, remailer service, or otherwise

.  
IF YOU OR ANYONE YOU KNOW IS “SPAMMED” BY SOMEONE WHO IS SELLING OR DESCRIBING THE COMPANY’S PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, PLEASE CONTACT US PROMPTLY SO THAT WE MAY TAKE APPROPRIATE ACTION.

compliance@AdzZoo.com 

## Compliance policy

At AdzZoo LLC (hereafter “the Company‘), we are committed to and singularly focused on building a brand that is widely recognized worldwide, while creating an business opportunity unparalleled by either conventional or network marketing standards. In doing so, there are compliance measures that need be enforced to protect the Company’s business opportunity for all.

## The Compliance Policy

Whereas the Company encourages the creation of any supplemental marketing material by any AdzZoo Independent Representative (hereafter “AIR”), the Company requires all advertising of any media type (including, but not limited to, printed or copied materials of any kind, newspapers, magazines, radio, Internet, television, video, etc.) be approved by the Company’s Compliance Department, prior to its publication or use. The Company reserves the right, at its discretion, to edit or discontinue previously approved AIR advertisements.

## Domain Policy

The word “AdzZoo” or any derivative thereof cannot be used in domain names.

## Enforcement

As these compliance policies are vital to the long-term stability of the Company and the preservation of the opportunity for all, violations of these policies will be strictly enforced. Failure to obtain approval for advertising material of any kind and/or failure to implement the policies in any material may result in the following:

> 1\. Formal warning letter and/or probation   
>  2\. Suspension of commissions  
>  3\. Termination of AIR position  
>  4\. Possible litigation
